John Landon Tardiff

Location: Warr Acres, OK Phone: (405)537-7274

Email: <u>JLandonTardiff@gmail.com</u>

Personal Website: https://stunning-parfait-198d49.netlifv.app

Software Engineering

Full-Stack Web Developer who graduated from Francis Tuttle Technology Center's Computer Science Academy as well as Francis Tuttle Technology Center's Programming and Software Development Course with a 4.0 GPA. Experienced in multiple languages and frameworks including C#, Javascript, React.js, ASP.NET MVC, and more. Self-motivated, quick learning, adaptable, with great leadership skills, and immense passion for the field.

Skills

<u>Programming Languages:</u> Java, C#, SQL Server, HTML, TypeScript, CSS, JavaScript <u>Frameworks:</u> Angular, .NET, Azure, React, ASP.NET MVC

Relevant Job Experience

05-2023 to present

Junior Software Developer - amshot

- •Used C#, Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL Server, React, ASP.NET MVC, and Angular to create and maintain applications used by clients
- •Worked on multiple client projects simultaneously, balancing workload and shifting priorities
- •Used Agile principles to manage time between multiple clients to ensure deadlines and expectations were met

05-2022 to 08-2022

Summer 2022 IT Intern - Devon Energy

- •Used Angular, .Net, and SQL to add features and fix bugs to a work order portal used by all on-site oil rig operators
- •Gained experience working on a large scale application that uses multiple different interconnected technologies and systems
- •Participated in volunteer work relating to STEM
- . Collaborated with a team to ensure a quality application was being produced
- •Exposed to multiple facets of the oil and gas industry
- •Made connections and attended social events within the company

Education

08-2021 to 05-2023

Francis Tuttle Technology Center/Programming and Software Development - Multiple Certifications in different programming languages and concepts 08-2018 to 05-2021

Francis Tuttle Technology Center/Computer Science Academy - Certificate of Achievement $\underline{08-2017}$ to $\underline{05-2021}$

Putnam City High School - High School Diploma (Honor Grad)